A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986, RG 37 FA1504
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1982-1986; 37; 327.55 Cubic Feet 857 containers
  - International Relations, 1982-1986; 15; 41.49 Cubic Feet 107 letter document boxes, 2 half-letter document boxes and 1 legal box
    - Countries/Continents, 2
      - Cuba (Box 350, Folder 6)
      - Europe - A-Z (Box 351, Folder 1)
      - Europe - European Security Study (Box 351, Folder 2-4)
      - Finland (Box 352, Folder 1)
      - France - A-Z (Box 352, Folder 2)
      - France - French-American Foundation (Box 352, Folder 3)
      - Germany (Box 352, Folder 4)
      - India (Box 352, Folder 5)
      - Ireland (Box 352, Folder 6)
      - Israel (Box 352, Folder 7)
      - Italy (Box 353, Folder 1)
      - Jamaica (Box 353, Folder 2)
      - Japan (Box 353, Folder 3)
      - Japan - A-Z (Box 353, Folder 4)
      - Japan - Japan Center for International Exchange, 1982 (Box 354, Folder 1)
      - Japan - Japan Society (Box 354, Folder 2)
      - Japan - Japan Society - A-Z, 1987 June (Box 354, Folder 3)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Board of Directors, 1982 (Box 355, Folder 1)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Contributions (Box 355, Folder 2)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Dinners-Luncheons (Box 355, Folder 3)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Fundraising (Box 355, Folder 4)
      - Japan - Japan Society - The Japan Foundation (Box 355, Folder 5)
      - Japan - Japan Society - 75th Anniversary - Blanchette H. Rockefeller (Box 355, Folder 6)
      - Japan - Japan Society - 75th Anniversary - David Rockefeller (Box 356, Folder 1)
      - Japan - Japan Society - Printed Matter (Box 356, Folder 2)
      - Middle East (Box 343, Folder 4)
      - Spain (Box 356, Folder 3)
      - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (USSR) (Box 356, Folder 4-5)
      - USSR - Focus on Society Reality (Box 357, Folder 1)
      - USSR - Informal US-Soviet Conference (Dartmouth Conference), 1981 (Box 357, Folder 2)
      - USSR - Informal US-Soviet Conference (Dartmouth XIV), 1984 (Box 357, Folder 3-4, Box 358, Folder 1)
      - USSR - Informal US-Soviet Conference (Dartmouth XIV), 1986 (Box 358, Folder 2-3, Box 359, Folder 1)
      - USSR - USA-USSR Citizen's Dialogue, Inc. (Box 359, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Aid, 3
      - Foreign Aid - A-I (Box 359, Folder 3-4)
      - Foreign Aid - J-Z (Box 360, Folder 1)
      - Care-Medico (Box 360, Folder 2)
      - Grassroots International (Box 360, Folder 3)
      - Oversees Development Council (Box 360, Folder 4)
      - Oxfam America (Box 360, Folder 5)
      - Meals for Millions-Freedom from Hunger Foundation (Box 361, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Policy, 4
      - Foreign Policy - A-Z (Box 361, Folder 2)
      - Committee for National Security - Contributions (Box 362, Folder 3)
      - Committee for National Security (Box 361, Folder 3, Box 362, Folder 1-2)
      - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc. (Box 362, Folder 4, Box 363, Folder 1-3)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Board of Directors, 1982-1983 (Box 363, Folder 4-5, Box 364, Folder 1)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Contributions (Box 364, Folder 2)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Contributions - New Approaches to Non-Proliferation Project (Box 364, Folder 3)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Finances, 1982 (Box 364, Folder 4)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Fellows Luncheon, 1982 (Box 365, Folder 1)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Foreign Affairs (Box 365, Folder 2-3)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Fund Raising, 1982-1983 (Box 366, Folder 1-2)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Luncheons, 1982 (Box 366, Folder 3)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Luncheons-Dinners, 1982-1985 (Box 366, Folder 4)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - McCloy, John J. (Box 366, Folder 5)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - President Search, 1985-1986 April (Box 367, Folder 1-3)
        Restricted - Open in 2026
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Meetings (Box 368, Folder 1)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Printed Matter (Box 368, Folder 2)
      - Council on Foreign Relations - Rockefeller, David - Retirement as Chairman (Box 368, Folder 3)
      - Foreign Policy Association (Box 368, Folder 4, Box 369, Folder 1)
    - Pan American, 5
      - Pan American - A-H (Box 369, Folder 2-4)
      - Pan American - I-O (Box 370, Folder 1-4)
      - Pan American - P-Z (Box 371, Folder 1)
      - Americas Society, 1981-1983 (Box 371, Folder 2-4, Box 372, Folder 1)
      - Americas Society - A-L (Box 372, Folder 2-4)
      - Americas Society - L-Z (Box 373, Folder 1-3)
      - Americas Society - Americas Society Foundation (Box 373, Folder 4)
      - Americas Society - Annual Report, 1986 (Box 373, Folder 5)
      - Americas Society - CICYP (Box 373, Folder 6)
      - Americas Society - Chairman's Council Meeting, 1983 (Box 373, Folder 7)
      - Americas Society - Chairman's Council Meeting, 1984 February 2 (Box 373, Folder 8)
      - Americas Society - Chairman's Council Meeting, South America, 1986 January 9-19 (Box 374, Folder 1)
      - Americas Society - Contributions (Box 374, Folder 2)
      - Americas Society - Cultural Council (Box 374, Folder 3)
      - Americas Society - Americas Society, Inc. - Debt Commission (Box 374, Folder 4-5, Box 375, Folder 1)
      - Americas Society - Dinners-Luncheons (Box 375, Folder 2)
      - Americas Society - Falkland Crisis (Box 375, Folder 3)
      - Americas Society - Friele, Berent (Box 375, Folder 4)
      - Americas Society - Fundraising (Box 375, Folder 5, Box 376, Folder 1)
      - Americas Society - Growth Study (Box 376, Folder 2-3)
      - Americas Society - Latin American Debt (Box 376, Folder 4)
      - Americas Society - McKinskey Report (Box 376, Folder 5)
      - Americas Society - Meetings (Box 377, Folder 1)
      - Americas Society - Miami Office (Box 377, Folder 2)
      - Americas Society - National Bipartian Commission on Central America (Box 377, Folder 3, Box 378, Folder 1-2)
      - Americas Society - Reorganization (Box 378, Folder 3)
      - Americas Society - Presidential Search (Box 379, Folder 1)
      - Public Affairs Advisory Committee (Box 380, Folder 1)
      - Trips - Panama, Costa Rica and Jamaica, 1986 October 28 (Box 380, Folder 2)
      - Trips - Vancouver, 1986 July 21-22 (Box 380, Folder 3)
      - Trips - Cleveland, 1986 June 25 (Box 380, Folder 4)
      - Trips - Uruguay, Argentina, Brazil, 1986 January 10-17 (Box 380, Folder 5)
      - Trips - Chicago, 1986 January 6-8 (Box 380, Folder 6)
      - Trips - Canada (Ottawa, Toronto, and Montreal), 1985 November 24-27 (Box 380, Folder 7)
      - Trips - San Francisco, 1985 September 16-18 (Box 381, Folder 1)
      - Trips - Chicago, 1983 October 31-November 1 (Box 381, Folder 2)
      - Trips, 1983 (Box 381, Folder 3)
      - Caribbean Basin Initiative (Box 381, Folder 4)
      - Caribbean Central American Action (Box 381, Folder 5, Box 382, Folder 1-2)
      - Caribbean Central American Action - Contributions (Box 382, Folder 3)
      - Caribbean Central American Action - Fundraising (Box 382, Folder 4)
      - Caribbean Central American Action - Miami Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 382, Folder 5)
      - Caribbean Central American Action - Miami Conference, 1985-1986 (Box 383, Folder 1)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc. (Box 383, Folder 2-3)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc. - CALA Conference, Montreal, 1982 September 13 (Box 383, Folder 4)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc. - Arthur Erickson Exhibit (Box 383, Folder 5)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc. - Contributions (Box 383, Folder 6)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc. - Finances (Box 384, Folder 1)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc. - Fundraising (Box 384, Folder 2)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc. - Meetings (Box 384, Folder 3)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc. - Printed Matter (Box 384, Folder 4)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc. - Spring Dance, 1982 May 27 (Box 384, Folder 5)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc. - Spring Party, 1983 (Box 385, Folder 1)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc. - Spring Party, 1984 May 23 (Box 385, Folder 2)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc. - Spring Party, 1985 June 6 (Box 385, Folder 3, Box 386, Folder 1)
      - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc. - Spring Party, 1986 (Box 386, Folder 2)
      - Council of the Americas, 1982 (Box 386, Folder 3)
      - Council of the Americas - Annual Report (Box 386, Folder 4)
      - Council of the Americas - David Rockefeller (Box 387, Folder 1-2)
      - Council of the Americas - Fund for Multinational Management Education Conference, 1984 September 21 (Box 387, Folder 3)
      - Council of the Americas - Meetings (Box 387, Folder 4)
      - Council of the Americas - U.S. Council of the Mexico-U.S. Business Committee (Box 388, Folder 1)
      - Council of the Americas - Washington Conference, 1986 May 5-6 (Box 388, Folder 2)
      - Council of the Americas - Washington Conference, 1985 May 21 (Box 388, Folder 3)
      - Council of the Americas - Washington Conference, 1984 May 8 (Box 388, Folder 4)
      - Council of the Americas - Washington Conference, 1983 June 1-2 (Box 388, Folder 5)
      - Council of the Americas - Washington Conference, 1982 June 21-22 (Box 389, Folder 1)
      - Inter-American Dialogue, 1980-1982 (Box 389, Folder 2)
      - Inter-American Dialogue, 1983 (Box 389, Folder 3)
      - Inter-American Dialogue, 1984-1986 (Box 390, Folder 1)
      - Pan American Society of the United States (Box 390, Folder 2)
      - Pan American Society - Gold Insigne (Box 390, Folder 3)
      - Pan American Union-OAS (Box 390, Folder 4)
      - Washington Office of Latin America, 1982-1986 (Box 391, Folder 1-2)
    - Peace, 6
      - Peace - A (Box 391, Folder 3)
      - Peace - A-J (Box 392, Folder 1-4)
      - Peace - K-O (Box 393, Folder 1-4)
      - Peace - P-S (Box 394, Folder 1-4)
      - Peace - T-Z (Box 395, Folder 1-2)
      - Academy for the Development of Global Peace (Box 395, Folder 3)
      - Access (Box 395, Folder 4)
      - American Committee on East-West Accord, 1986 (Box 395, Folder 5)
      - American Committee on East-West Accord, 1985 (Box 396, Folder 1)
      - American Committee on East-West Accord, 1982-1984 (Box 396, Folder 2)
      - American Council of Washington, 1982 (Box 397, Folder 1)
      - Arizona Center to Reverse the Arms Race (Box 397, Folder 2)
      - Arms Control Association (Box 397, Folder 3-5, Box 398, Folder 1)
      - Athletes United for Peace (Box 398, Folder 2-4, Box 399, Folder 1)
      - Better World Society (Box 399, Folder 2)
      - Bilderberg - General, 1978-1984 (Box 399, Folder 3)
      - Bilderberg Conference - Meetings, 1982 (Box 399, Folder 4)
      - Bilderberg - Meetings, 1983 (Box 400, Folder 1)
      - Bilderberg Meetings - Sweden, 1984 (Box 400, Folder 2)
      - Bilderberg Conference - Meetings - Contributions, 1977 (Box 400, Folder 3)
      - Business Executives for National Security Education Fund, Inc. (Box 400, Folder 4, Box 401, Folder 1-4, Box 402, Folder 1)
      - CALC Foundation (Clergy and Laity Concerned) (Box 402, Folder 2)
      - Californians for a Bilateral Nuclear Weapons Freeze (Box 402, Folder 3)
      - Cambridge Commission on Nuclear Disarmament and Peace Education (Box 402, Folder 4)
      - Citizen Alert (Box 402, Folder 5)
      - Center for Innovative Diplomacy (Box 403, Folder 1-2)
      - Citizen Exchange Council, Inc. (Box 403, Folder 3)
      - Citizens Against Nuclear War, 1982-1986 (Box 404, Folder 1-2)
      - Committee for a Strong Peaceful America (Box 404, Folder 3)
      - Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility (Box 405, Folder 1)
      - Council for a Livable World Education Fund (Box 405, Folder 2)
      - Council for a Livable World Education Fund - Contributions (Box 405, Folder 3)
      - Down Winder, 1984 (Box 405, Folder 4)
      - Down Winder, 1985-1986 (Box 406, Folder 1)
      - Educators for Social Responsibility (Box 406, Folder 2-3)
      - Educators for Social Responsibility - Contributions (Box 407, Folder 1-2)
      - The Elbe Alliance (Box 408, Folder 1)
      - Forum Foundation (Box 408, Folder 2-3)
      - Forum Foundation - Contributions (Box 409, Folder 1)
      - Foundation for the Arts of Peace (Box 409, Folder 2-3)
      - Fund for Peace (Box 410, Folder 1)
      - Ground Zero (Box 410, Folder 2-3)
      - Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry (Box 411, Folder 1-2)
      - Hehir, J. Bryan (Box 411, Folder 3)
      - Institute for Defense and Disarmament Studies (Box 411, Folder 4, Box 412, Folder 1)
      - Institute for Security and Cooperation in Outer Space (Box 412, Folder 2)
      - Institute for World Order (Box 412, Folder 3)
      - Institute for Space and Security Studies (Box 413, Folder 1-2)
      - International Peace Academy (Box 413, Folder 3)
      - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War (Box 414, Folder 1-4)
      - Jobs with Peace, Inc. (Box 415, Folder 1-4)
      - Lawyers Alliance for Nuclear Arms Control, Inc. (Box 415, Folder 5, Box 416, Folder 1-3)
      - Lawyers Committee on Nuclear Policy (Box 416, Folder 4)
      - Local Elected Officials for Social Responsibility (Box 417, Folder 1)
      - Microsecond (Box 417, Folder 2)
      - Musicians Against Nuclear Arms (Box 417, Folder 3)
      - The Nation Institute (Box 417, Folder 4)
      - National Campaign to Save the ABM Treaty (Box 418, Folder 1)
      - National Catholic Education Association (Box 418, Folder 2)
      - National Committee for Radiation Victims (Box 418, Folder 3)
      - National Mobilization for Survival (Box 418, Folder 4)
      - National Student Action Center (Box 419, Folder 1)
      - National Women's Conference and Preventing Nuclear War (Box 419, Folder 2)
      - New Century Policies Educational Programs, Inc. (Box 419, Folder 3)
      - Nobel Peace Prize (Box 419, Folder 4)
      - Norwich Center (Box 419, Folder 5)
      - Nuclear Arms Monitor (Box 419, Folder 6)
      - Nuclear Control Institute (Box 420, Folder 1-5, Box 421, Folder 1)
      - Nuclear Freeze Foundation, Inc. (Box 421, Folder 2)
      - The Nuclear Network (Box 421, Folder 3)
      - Nuclear Free Zones (Box 421, Folder 4)
      - Nuclear Psychology Program, Inc. (Box 422, Folder 1)
      - Nuclear Times (Box 421, Folder 5)
      - Nuclear Weapons Education Fund, Inc. (Box 422, Folder 2-3)
      - Nuclear Weapons Education Fund of Downstate New York (Box 422, Folder 4)
      - Oak Ridge Peace Conservation Group (Box 423, Folder 1)
      - Parliamentarians for World Order Conference Fund (Box 423, Folder 2-3)
      - Peace Child Foundation (Box 424, Folder 1)
      - Peace and Common Security (Box 424, Folder 2)
      - Peace Corps Institute (Box 424, Folder 3)
      - Peace Development Fund (Box 425, Folder 1-3)
      - Peace Links (Box 426, Folder 1-2)
      - The Peace Museum (Box 426, Folder 3)
      - Peace PAC (Box 426, Folder 4)
      - The Peace Through Law Education Fund (Box 426, Folder 5)
      - Peacenet (Box 426, Folder 6)
      - Performing Arts for Nuclear Disarmament (Box 427, Folder 1)
      - Petrie, Donald A. (Box 427, Folder 2)
      - Planet Earth Foundation (Box 427, Folder 3)
      - Ploughshares Fund (Box 427, Folder 4)
      - Plowshares Institute (Box 427, Folder 5)
      - Richard Pollock Associates, Inc. (Box 428, Folder 1)
      - Propeace (Box 428, Folder 2)
      - Sane (Box 428, Folder 3-4, Box 429, Folder 1)
      - Search for Common Ground (Box 429, Folder 2)
      - Samantha Smith Foundation (Box 429, Folder 3)
      - Southeast Project on Human Needs and Peace (Box 429, Folder 4)
      - Southern California Unions for Jobs with Peace and Nuclear Weapons Freeze (Box 429, Folder 5)
      - Student-Teacher Organization to Prevent Nuclear War (Box 430, Folder 1)
      - Survival Education Fund (Box 430, Folder 2)
      - UCAM Educational Association (Box 430, Folder 3)
      - U.S. Pacific Issues Network (Box 431, Folder 1)
      - Up with People (Box 431, Folder 2)
      - Klein Walker Associates (Box 431, Folder 3)
      - Women for a Meaningful Summit (Box 431, Folder 4)
      - Western Solidarity (Box 432, Folder 1)
      - Women's Action for Nuclear Disarmament Education Fund (Box 432, Folder 2, Box 433, Folder 1)
      - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (Box 432, Folder 3)
      - Woolman Hill, Inc. (Box 433, Folder 2)
      - World Policy Institute (Box 433, Folder 3)
      - World Policy Institute - Alida R. Dayton (Box 434, Folder 1)
        Restricted - Living Rockefeller family members
      - World Policy Institute - Sandra R. Ferry (Box 434, Folder 2)
      - World Policy Institute - World Without War Council, Inc. (Box 434, Folder 3)
    - United Nations, 7
      - United Nations - A-Z (Box 435, Folder 1-3)
      - United Nations Association of the United States of America (Box 435, Folder 4)
      - UNICEF (Box 436, Folder 1)
    - United States Government, 8
      - Agency for International Development (AID) (Box 436, Folder 2)
      - Agency for International Development (AID) - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) (Box 436, Folder 3)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC), 1982-1984 (Box 436, Folder 4-5)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Dinner F. Pace, 1982 (Box 437, Folder 1)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Meetings - Annual, 1982-1983 (Box 437, Folder 2)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Meetings - Board of Directors, 1981-1984 (Box 437, Folder 3-5)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Meetings - Board of Directors Council, 1984 (Box 438, Folder 1)
      - International Executive Service Corps (IESC) - Memberships, 1984 (Box 438, Folder 2)
      - Executive Council on Foreign Diplomats (Box 438, Folder 3)
      - Department of State - General (Box 438, Folder 4)
      - The Commission of Security and Economic Assistance (Carlucci Commission) (Box 438, Folder 5)
      - Department of State - Commission on Security and Economic Assistance (Box 439, Folder 1-2, Box 440, Box 441, Box 442, Folder 1)
      - Department of State - Commission on Security and Economic Assistance - Meeting 1984, 1984 November 14 (Box 442, Folder 2)
      - Department of State - Commission on Security and Economic Assistance - Meetings 1983 (Box 442, Folder 3-4, Box 443, Folder 1-7, Box 444, Folder 1-2)
      - Department of State - Fine Arts Committee (Box 444, Folder 3-4)
      - President's International Youth Exchange Initiative (Box 445, Folder 1)
  - J-M, 1982-1986; 16; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - J - Miscellaneous (Box 445, Folder 2)
    - K - Miscellaneous (Box 445, Folder 3)
    - L - Miscellaneous (Box 445, Folder 4)
    - M - Miscellaneous (Box 445, Folder 5)
  - Medicine, 1982-1986; 17; 26.2 Cubic Feet 68 letter document boxes and 2 half-letter boxes
    - Medicine - A-Z, 1
      - Medicine - A (Box 445, Folder 6)
      - Medicine - B-C (Box 446, Folder 1-3)
      - Medicine - D-H (Box 447, Folder 1-3)
      - Medicine - J-M (Box 448, Folder 1-4)
      - Medicine - N-Z (Box 449, Folder 1-3)
      - AIDS Medical Foundation (Box 450, Folder 1)
      - Alcohol and Drug Awareness Program for the Tarrytowns (Box 450, Folder 2)
      - Alzheimer's Disease and Related Disorders Association, Inc. (Box 450, Folder 3)
      - American Cancer Society (Box 450, Folder 4)
      - American College of Nurse-Midwifes (Box 450, Folder 5)
      - American Cancer Society - New York City Division (Box 451, Folder 1)
      - American Diabetes Association (Box 451, Folder 2)
      - American Heart Association (Box 451, Folder 3)
      - Arthritis Foundation and Chapters (Box 451, Folder 4)
      - Cancer Care (Box 451, Folder 5)
      - Center for Psychosocial Studies (Box 452, Folder 1)
      - Gay Men's Health Crisis, Restricted - Living Rockefeller family members (Box 455, Folder 1)
      - General Motors Cancer Research Foundation (Box 452, Folder 2)
      - House Ear Institute (Box 452, Folder 3, Box 453, Folder 1)
      - Institute for the Advancement of Health - Laurance S. Rockefeller (Box 453, Folder 2)
      - Institute for the Advancement of Health - Printed Matter (Box 453, Folder 3, Box 454, Folder 1)
      - Mental Illness Counseling Center (Box 454, Folder 2)
      - Institute for Advancement of Health (Box 456, Folder 1)
      - National Association of Patients on Hemodialysis and Transplantation (Box 454, Folder 3)
      - National Center for Health Education (Box 454, Folder 4)
      - National Foundation for Cancer Research (Box 454, Folder 5)
      - National Gay Health Education Foundation (Box 457, Folder 1)
      - New York Academy of Medicine (Box 457, Folder 2)
      - New York Blood Center (Box 457, Folder 3)
      - New York Blood Center - Meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 457, Folder 4-5)
      - New York Blood Center - Minutes-Meetings, 1983-1986 (Box 458, Folder 1-4)
      - New York Blood Center - Printed Matter (Box 458, Folder 5)
      - Nurses Environmental Health Watch (Box 459, Folder 1-2)
      - Linus Pauling Institute of Science and Medicine (Box 459, Folder 2)
      - Physicians for Social Responsibility (Box 459, Folder 3-4)
      - Physicians for Social Responsibility - Printed Matter (Box 460, Folder 1)
      - Project Orbis (Box 460, Folder 2)
      - RP Foundation Fighting Blindness (Box 460, Folder 3)
      - Project Orbis - Printed Matter (Box 461, Folder 1)
      - Salk Institute (Box 461, Folder 2)
      - Shepherd Spinal Center (Box 461, Folder 3)
      - Society for the Right to Die (Box 462, Folder 1)
      - United Cerebral Palsy of New York City (Box 462, Folder 2)
      - United States Government - Department of Health and Human Services (Box 462, Folder 3)
      - The Voice Foundation (Box 462, Folder 4)
    - Alcoholism, 2
      - Alcoholism - A-Z (Box 463, Folder 1)
      - Alcoholism Council of Greater New York (Box 463, Folder 2)
      - Children of Alcoholics Foundation (Box 463, Folder 3, Box 464, Folder 1)
      - Children of Alcoholics Foundation - Laurance S. Rockefeller (Box 464, Folder 2)
      - Freedom Institute (Box 464, Folder 3)
      - Mothers Against Drunk Drivers (MADD) (Box 464, Folder 4, Box 465, Folder 1)
      - National Council on Alcoholism (Box 465, Folder 2-4, Box 466, Folder 1)
      - National Council on Alcoholism - Cambridge Associates (Box 466, Folder 2)
      - National Council on Alcoholism - Fundraising - Luncheon For Foundations, 1986 January 26 (Box 466, Folder 3)
      - National Council on Alcoholism - New York City Affiliate, Inc. (Box 466, Folder 4)
      - National Council on Alcoholism - Laurance S. Rockefeller (Box 467, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals, 3
      - Hospitals - A-L (Box 467, Folder 2-5)
      - Hospitals - M-R (Box 468, Folder 1-4)
      - Hospitals - S-Z (Box 469, Folder 1)
      - Children's Medical Center, Boston (Box 469, Folder 2)
      - Columbia Presbyterian Medical Center (Box 469, Folder 3)
      - Columbia Presbyterian Medical Center - Printed Matter (Box 469, Folder 4)
      - Columbia Presbyterian Medical Center - Presbyterian Hospital in the City of New York (Box 469, Folder 5)
      - Eisenhower Medical Center (Box 470, Folder 1)
      - Eisenhower Medical Center - Printed Matter (Box 470, Folder 2)
      - John's Hopkins Hospital (Box 470, Folder 3)
      - Inter-Institutional Policy Committee (Box 470, Folder 4)
      - Maine Medical Center, Portland, Maine (Box 470, Folder 5)
      - The Hospital for Special Surgery (Box 471, Folder 1)
      - Manhattan Eye, Ear and Throat Hospital (Box 471, Folder 2)